<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Avraam Marimpis</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Avraam Marimpis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 22:56:13 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Life</title>
      <link>/life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 22:56:13 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/life/</guid>
      <description>I like spending time with a cup of coffee in my hands.
(written after spending some time with a cup of coffee in my hands)
 I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying life with my better half in Maastricht, The Netherlands. I love spending time with her, when traveling (and getting lost with Google Maps), &amp;ldquo;cooking&amp;rdquo;, dancing (usually showing off in front of the dj) and watching doggos-related videos on YouTube :D.
Running (something like trailing) is an essential aspect of my daily life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 22:56:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Below, I would like to list some of my most important and close to my heart projects, that I have spearheaded or just participated. Some of these projects are still in active development, while others are presented because I feel nostalgic about them.
dyfunconn: Dynamic Functional Connectivity - A NeuroImaging Python Module dyfunconn is a Python module for your EEG/fMRI/and MEG-i-guess connectivity and graph analysis needs. It is organized into a few sub-modules; the most obvious ones are the fc for functional connectivity and graph for the graph-related algos: graph distances and thresholding schemes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 20:05:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>The last years I find myself being most productive and decisive to pursue Ph.D. studies. I am currently affiliated with the Cognitive Neuroscience Department, at the Faculty of Neuroscience of Maastricht University, and, at the same time, employed at Brain Innovation B.V. in Maastricht.
My main research focus is brain connectivity and graph theory (and algorithms and applications). The way connectivity varies and changes across brain regions given a cognitive task, mental load, and even neurodegenerative disease.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>